gadgettown.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Notice : GadgetTown.com

GadgetTown.com is firmly committed to the privacy and security of your personal info in our site. For your full understanding, the following statement details how we collect and use information, as well as the security measures we take to assure that your information stays secure and private.

Information Collected  
When you make a purchase from GadgetTown.com, we collect your name and payment method information, such as credit card information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s). We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Information Use  
Information we collect may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:  
1\. Deliver products and services that you purchase online  
2\. Register you as a member of GadgetTown.com  
3\. Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchases  
4\. Confirm your orders  
5\. Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests  
6\. Communicate great values and featured items to you  
7\. Find and stock the products you want  
8\. Customize your shopping experience

Security  
Your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet by SSL. When you enter GadgetTown.com, any personal information including, address, telephone number, Social Security or EIN number, account number or other information that personally identifies you, is secured through data encryption technology. This protection applies in areas such as, but not limited to, online ordering, order status, and credit application. The Site contains links to other Web sites, and GadgetTown.com is not responsible for content or privacy practices on those third party Web sites. You may wish to review their respective privacy policies, as well.

Cookies   
Cookie technology can provide you with tailored information while visiting a Web site. Cookies are data elements that a Web site can send to your browser and are stored on your system. Some Web site pages use cookies to better serve you when you return to our Site. The Site cookie sent to your address contains what country location you have selected and if you have selected on-line settings for visiting the Site. The Site does not store individual names, email addresses, street addresses, credit card numbers, or phone numbers in cookies placed on your computer. However, the Site does collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we track the domains people visit and we measure visitor activity on the Site, but we do so in ways that keep personal information non-identifiable. GadgetTown.com uses this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.

Information Update  
If we change or update this Privacy Notice, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use, and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Notice has been changed or updated.

Questions & Feedback  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about Privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at info@GadgetTown.com.
